Guide to the Blukis Onat Applied Sciences (BOAS), Inc. Papers 1968-2010
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Olympic National Forest and Olympic National Park, Background Documents on Ethnography and Archaeology, Blukis Archaeological Consulting Service: black and white negative and print; and drafts of bibliography (draft) and archaeological research design., circa 1978 (Box-folder 1/12, Project 197802)
- Northern Tier Pipeline Project Review by Blukis Archaeological Consulting Service: preliminary documents regarding the effect on cultural resources; copy of proposed Memorandum of Agreement between State Historic Preservation Officer and Northern Tier Pipeline Company., undated, 1979 (Box-folder 1/13, Project 197803)
- Wing Point Fairway View, Planned Unit Development Project, Archaeological Reconnaissance by Blukis Archaeological Consulting Service, Kitsap County: map of development; 1-page report., undated, 1977 (Box-folder 1/14, Project 197804)
- Site 45SK31, Gymnasium Expansion Survey by Blukis Archaeological Consulting Service, Swinomish Indian Tribal Community, Skagit County: 2-page letter report., 1978 March (Box-folder 1/15, Project 197805)
- Site 45SK22 and Lone Tree Point/Tosi Point, Archaeological Field Reconnaissance of the Thousand Trails property by Blukis Archaeological Consulting Service for Pacific Rim Group, Inc., Fidalgo Island, Skagit County: 5-page report., circa 1978 (Box-folder 2/1, Project 197806)
- Site 45JE16, Archaeological Excavations by Washington Archaeological Research Center, Indian Island, Jefferson County: report and newspaper article regarding reburial in 2000., 1977, 2000 October (Box-folder 2/2, Project 197808)
- Skagit Regional Airport, Cultural Resources Reconnaissance by Blukis Archaeological Consulting Service, Bayview, Skagit County: color slides and report., 1979 (Box-folder 2/3, Project 197901)
- 45CL98/99 and Historic Sites Affected by Delanoy Estates Development, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance by Blukis Archaeological Consulting Service for McKay and Sposito Company, Clark County: site forms and report., 1979 (Box-folder 2/4, Project 197902)
- 45CL98/99 and Historic Sites Affected by Delanoy Estates Development, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance for McKay and Sposito Company, Clark County: 2 boxes artifacts (lithics)., 1979 (Box-folder 72/1-2, Project 197902)
- Site 45SJ269, Initial Site Examination, Decatur Island, San Juan County: 5-page report with cost estimate for excavation., 1979 (Box-folder 2/5, Project 197903)
- Anacortes Marina Site, Archaeological Reconnaissance by Blukis Archaeological Consulting Service, Skagit County: black and white negatives and contact sheet; color slides; map; 1-page report., circa 1979 (Box-folder 2/6, Project 197904 (see also 198101))
- Skagit River Levee and Channel Improvement Project, Cultural Resources Reconnaissance for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers by Seattle Central Community College, Skagit County: correspondence; field notes; project map; bibliographic review and field reconnaissance, cultural resources survey, and supplemental cultural resources reconnaissance reports., 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2/7-11, Project 197905, 197905.1, 197905.2, 197905.3)
- Skagit River Levee and Channel Improvement Project, Cultural Resources Reconnaissance for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers by Seattle Central Community College, Skagit County: plates and figures for 197905.1., 1979 (Box-folder 73/1, Project 197905)
- Washington Public Power Supply System (WPPSS) Nuclear Projects 3 and 5, Archaeological Monitoring by Institute of Cooperative Research, primarily Grays Harbor County: correspondence; field forms; maps; black and white negatives, prints, and contact sheets; field notebooks; site forms; and 1979-1980 and 1980-1981 reports., 1969, 1970, 1973-1975, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 3/1-8, Project 197906 (see also 198103, 198104), 197906.1, 197906.2)
- WPPSS Nuclear Projects 3 and 5, Archaeological Monitoring by Institute of Cooperative Research, primarily Grays Harbor County: aerial photographs., 1969, 1974 (Box-folder 75/1, Project 197906)
- WPPSS Nuclear Projects 3 and 5, Archaeological Monitoring by Institute of Cooperative Research, primarily Grays Harbor County: project diazo prints., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 75/2, Project 197906)
- WPPSS Nuclear Projects 3 and 5, Archaeological Monitoring by Institute of Cooperative Research, Grays Harbor County: project diazo print; drafting film; map of archaeological testing., 1979-1980 (Box-folder 75/3, Project 197906)
- WPPSS Nuclear Projects 3 and 5, Archaeological Monitoring, Grays Harbor County: diazo prints of powerline with archaeological data annotations., circa 1979-1980 (Box-folder 75/4, Project 197906)
- East Arlington Regional Park Excavations, Archaeological Monitoring by Seattle Central Community College, Arlington, Snohomish County: correspondence; site form; report., 1979-1980 (Box-folder 3/9, Project 197907)
- The Skagit: Wild and Scenic River Study Report by U.S. Department of Agriculture, Forest Service: report., circa 1975 (Box-folder 4/1, Project 198001)
- RESTRICTED -- Skagit Wild and Scenic River, Cultural Resource Overview and Sample Survey by the Institute for Cooperative Research for Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest: 3-volume report., 1980 (Box-folder 57R/1-2, Project 198001)
  This material may not be accessed without permission, please contact MASC for details
- Satsop Integrating Transmission Project, Cultural Resource Overview and Archaeological Survey performed by Institute for Cooperative Research under Washington Archaeological Research Center for Bonneville Power Administration: report., 1980 (Box-folder 4/2, Project 198003)
- Satsop Integrating Transmission Project, Cultural Resource Overview and Archaeological Survey performed by Institute for Cooperative Research under Washington Archaeological Research Center for Bonneville Power Administration: Field maps - USGS 15' and 7.5' topographic maps., circa 1980 (Box-folder 75/5, Project 198003)
- Anacortes Marina Site, Archaeological Reconnaissance, Skagit County: 4-page report; site forms., circa 1981 (Box-folder 4/3, Project 198101 (see also 197904))
- Cedar Falls Headwaters Improvement Project, Archaeological Field Reconnaissance, King County, for Seattle City Light Department: black and white negatives and prints; and 4-page report., 1981 (Box-folder 4/4, Project 198102)
- Keyes Road Bridge Right of Way and the Fuller Bridge Site (45GH34), Archaeological Testing and Reconnaissance by Institute for Cooperative Research for Washington Public Power Supply System (WPPSS), Grays Harbor County: testing plan for 45GH34 and field notebook; report., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 4/5, Project 198103 (see also 197906 and 198104))
- Keyes Road Bridge Right of Way and the Flink Farm Site (45GH40), Archaeological Testing and Excavation by Institute for Cooperative Research for Washington Public Power Supply System (WPPSS), Grays Harbor County: field notes; field forms; black and white negatives, contact sheet, and prints; color slides; diazo print; report., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 4/6, Project 198104 (see also 197906 and 198103))
- Keyes Road Bridge Right of Way and the Flink Farm Site (45GH40), Archaeological Testing and Excavation by Institute for Cooperative Research for Washington Public Power Supply System (WPPSS), Grays Harbor County: diazo prints of project area and field map overlays., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 75/6, Project 198104)
- 45SJ185, Archaeological Site Survey, San Juan County: original and revised site forms; deed; correspondence; color slides., 1951, 1975, 1981, 2012 (Box-folder 4/7, Project 198201)
- Proposed Taneum/Manastash Land Exchange between Wenatchee National Forest and BN Timberlands Inc., Cultural Resource Survey, Kittitas County: black and white negatives and prints; report, original and bound copy., 1982 (Box-folder 4/8, Project 198202)
- Falls Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: correspondence and report., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5/1, Project 198203.1)
- Upper and Lower Rocky Creek Water Power Projects, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: color slides and report., 1982 (Box-folder 5/2, Project 198203.2)
- Rocky Creek Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: report., 1983 (Box-folder 5/3, Project 198203.3)
- Racehorse Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: notes; correspondence; report., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5/4, Project 198204.1)
- Deadhorse Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: correspondence and report., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5/5, Project 198204.2)
- Boulder Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: report., 1982 (Box-folder 5/6, Project 198204.3)
- Damnation Creek Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Ross Lake National Recreation Area, Skagit County: report., 1982 (Box-folder 5/7, Project 198205.1)
- Thornton Creek Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Ross Lake National Recreation Area, Skagit County: correspondence and report., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5/8, Project 198205.2)
- Glacier Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: correspondence regarding consultation with tribes; maps; color slides; report., 1982, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 5/9, Project 198206.1 and 198603 (see also 198207 and 198208))
- Canyon Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: correspondence and report., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 5/10, Project 198206.2)
- Ruth Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: correspondence and report., 1982 (Box-folder 5/11, Project 198207 (see also 198206.1,198208))
- Swamp Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: map and report., 1982 (Box-folder 5/12, Project 198208 (see also 198206.1,198207))
- Wells Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: correspondence and report., 1982, 1984 (Box-folder 5/13, Project 198209)
- Limekiln Property, Archaeological Survey, San Juan Island: site form; notes; 2-page report., 1983 (Box-folder 5/14, Project 198301)
- Mt. Baker Geothermal Project, Consultation with Native American Smokehouse Groups for Seattle City Light: color slides; correspondence; background literature on geothermal resources; map; report., 1983-1984 (Box-folder 5/15, Project 198302)
- Battelle Marine Research Laboratories, especially Site 45CA277 (Suxtcikwi'in), Cultural Resources Overview, Sequim, Clallam County: correspondence; consultant agreement; proposals., 1980-1985 (Box-folder 5/16, Project 198303 (see also 198413))
- Burton Creek Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Snohomish County: correspondence and report., 1983 (Box-folder 5/17, Project 198305)
- Bagley Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: reports., 1983-1984 (Box-folder 5/18, Project 198306)
- Little White Salmon Creek, Willard Fish Hatchery, Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Skamania County: field notes; site form; report., 1983 (Box-folder 5/19, Project 198307)
- Quartz Creek Hydro Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Snohomish County: correspondence and report., 1983 (Box-folder 5/20, Project 198308)
- Diobsud Creek Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Skagit County: report., 1983 (Box-folder 5/21, Project 198309)
- North Fork Snoqualmie River Municipal Water Supply Project, Historical and Archaeological Resources Overview and Field Reconnaissance of the Reservoir, Penstock, Pipeline, and Powerhouse Locations for the City of Bellevue, King County: black and white negatives and prints; correspondence; field notes; maps; report., 1984, 1985, 2001 (Box-folder 6/1-2, Project 198401)
- North Fork Snoqualmie River Municipal Water Supply Project, Historical and Archaeological Resources Overview and Field Reconnaissance of the Reservoir, Penstock, Pipeline, and Powerhouse Locations for the City of Bellevue, King County: diazo prints of project areas., undated, 1984 (Box-folder 75/7, Project 198401)
- Areas 3A and 3B (Foster Golf Course) of Renton Effluent Transfer System (ETS), Cultural Resource Investigations for URS Engineers under contract with METRO Transit, King County: correspondence; proposals for work; 8-page letter report., 1984-1985 (Box-folder 6/3, Project 198403.1 (see also 198601))
- ETS-4A/4B, 6, 7, 8A/8B, 9, and 10 of Renton Effluent Transfer System (ETS), Cultural Resource and Historic Structure Evaluation for URS Engineers under contract with METRO Transit, King County: report., 1985 (Box-folder 6/4, Project 198403.2)
- Site 45KI267 and ETS-3C/3D of Renton Effluent Transfer System (ETS), Cultural Resource Evaluations for URS Engineers under contract with METRO Transit, King County: reports., 1985 (Box-folder 6/5, Project 198403.3 and 198403.3a)
- Renton Effluent Transfer System (ETS) and National Register of Historic Places Property Duwamish No. 1 Site (45KI23), Cultural Resource Data Recovery Program (backhoe trench, excavation, monitoring, testing) for URS Engineers under contract with METRO Transit, King County: correspondence; proposals; and report., 1983, 1985, 2001, 2002 (Box-folder 6/6, Project 198403.4)
- Port Gardner Area, US Navy, Archaeological and Historical Cultural Resources Survey, Everett, Snohomish County: maps and report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/7, Project 198404.1)
- Sand Point Naval Air Station, Archaeological and Historical Cultural Resources Survey, King County: background document and report., 1983-1984 (Box-folder 6/8, Project 198404.2)
- Pier 90 and 91 Terminals at Smith Cove, US Navy, Archaeological and Historical Cultural Resources Survey, King County: maps and report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/9, Project 198404.3)
- Proposed Cathcart Sanitary Landfill, Site Area F, Cultural Resources Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Snohomish County: field notes; maps; preliminary report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/10, Project 198405.1)
- Proposed Cathcart Sanitary Landfill, Site Area F, Cultural Resources, Snohomish County: final report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/11, Project 198405.2)
- Skyport/Pickering Park, Archaeological and Historical Resources, Issaquah, King County: National Register of Historic Properties Nomination Form for Pickering Farm; maps; draft report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/12, Project 198406)
- Swinomish Housing - 5 acre site, Cultural Resources, Skagit County: report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/13, Project 198407)
- Coyote and Ski View Timber Sale Planning Areas, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance, Okanogan-Wenatchee National Forest, Kittitas County: field notes; maps; report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/14, Project 198408)
- Yarrow Village Project, Cultural Resource Assessment, King County: report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/15, Project 198409)
- Skagit Salmon Hatchery, Cascade River Intake, Cultural Resources Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Skagit County: correspondence; field notes; maps; report., 1981, 1984 (Box-folder 6/16, Project 198410)
- Owl Creek Small Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Washington State Department of Natural Resources, Jefferson County: map and report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/17, Project 198411.1)
- Dungeness River Small Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Olympic National Forest, Clallam County: maps and report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/18, Project 198411.2)
- Segelsen Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resources Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Snohomish and Skagit Counties: correspondence and report., 1984 (Box-folder 6/19, Project 198412)
- 45CA227 and Other Cultural Resources, Testing and Evaluation, Battelle Marine Research Laboratories, Washington Harbor, Sequim, Clallam County: correspondence and report., 1984, 1995, 1996 (Box-folder 6/20, Project 198413.1)
- 12,000 Years of Land Use:brochure prepared for Battelle Pacific Northwest Division., 1984 (Box-folder 6/21, Project 198413.2)
- Silver Creek Small Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resources Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Olympic National Forest, Clallam County: background document and report., 1982, 1984 (Box-folder 7/1, Project 198414)
- Reservoir Site and Harry Yabeelt Logging Unit, Cultural Resource Survey, Swinomish Reservation: report., 1984 (Box-folder 7/2, Project 198415)
- Tyler Peak Small Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resources Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Olympic National Forest, Clallam County: background document and report., undated, 1984 (Box-folder 7/3, Project 198416)
- Rim Road Logging Unit, Cultural Resources Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Muckleshoot Indian Reservation: correspondence; maps; report., 1984 (Box-folder 7/4, Project 198417)
- Site 45JE16 Indian Island, Site Visit and Archaeological Assessment for the Department of the Navy, Jefferson County: correspondence and 1-page report., 1984-1985 (Box-folder 7/5, Project 198501)
- Winslow Waterfront Park Improvements, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance, Kitsap County: diazo prints; maps; correspondence; field notes; newspaper article; report., 1977, 1985 (Box-folder 7/6, Project 198502)
- Mt. Baker Geothermal Project, Native American Consultation (Lummi, Nooksack, Samish, Sauk-Suiattle, Swinomish, and Upper Skagit), for Seattle City Light: correspondence; notes; background documents; and report., 1985-1986 (Box-folder 7/7, Project 198505)
- Lakota Wastewater Treatment Plant Expansion Phase III, Cultural Resources Reconnaissance for Lakehaven Sewer District, King County: correspondence; map; background documents; report., 1980, 1985 (Box-folder 7/8, Project 198507)
- Excelsior Mountain Hydroelectric Project, FERC No. 5338, Cultural Resources Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Snohomish County: correspondence; maps; report., 1982, 1984, 1985 (Box-folder 7/9, Project 198508)
- Jordan Creek Small Hydro Project, Cultural Resources Literature Search and Field Reconnaissance for Cascades Environmental Services, Skagit County: correspondence; field notes; map; report., 1983, 1985 (Box-folder 7/10, Project 198509)
- Renton Effluent Transfer System (ETS) and National Register of Historic Places Property Duwamish No. 1 Site (45KI23), Cultural Resources Data Recovery Plan, METRO Transit (King County); 45KI267 and Foster Golf Course, Renton Effluent Transfer System (ETS), Cultural Resource Investigation, METRO Transit, King County: correspondence, request for proposal; and proposals., 1985 (Box-folder 7/11-12, Project 198601.1 (see also 198403.4))
- Renton Effluent Transfer System (ETS) and Duwamish No. 1 Site (45KI23), Protest of Bid Award on Data Recovery, METRO Transit (King County): correspondence and documents connected to BOAS protest of not being awarded contract., 1985 (Box-folder 7/13, Project 198601.1a)
- Renton Effluent Transfer System (ETS) and National Register of Historic Places Property Duwamish No. 1 Site (45KI23), 1986 Data Recovery for URS Engineers under contract with METRO Transit, King County: newspaper articles and report., 1987 (Box-folder 8/1-2, Project 198601.2)
- Renton Effluent Transfer System, Archaeological Monitoring for URS Engineers under contract with METRO Transit, King County: report., 1987 (Box-folder 8/3, Project 198601.3)
- Swinomish Channel Marina, Cultural Resources Survey, Swinomish Reservation, Skagit County: report., 1986 (Box-folder 8/4, Project 198602)
- Kwina Road Improvements, Lummi Indian Reservation, Cultural Resource Assessment, Whatcom County: report., 1986 (Box-folder 8/5, Project 198604)
- Northern Puget Sound Study Unit, Resource Protection Planning Process (RP3), Identification of Prehistoric Archaeological Resources, San Juan, Island, Whatcom, Skagit, and Snohomish Counties: report., 1987 (Box-folder 8/6, Project 198606)
- SE 208th St., Kent, Archaeological Monitoring for Scoccolo Construction, Inc., King County: field notes and 2-page report., 1986 (Box-folder 8/7, Project 198607)
- Road Improvements and Sites 45KP21, 45KP22, 45KP23, Cultural Resource Assessment, Port Gamble Indian Reservation, Kitsap County., 1986, 2011 (Box-folder 8/8, Project 198608.1)
- Kwina Road Improvements, Lummi Indian Reservation, Cultural Resource Assessment, Whatcom County: report., 1986 (Box-folder 8/9, Project 198608.2)
- Mission Beach Road Improvements, Tulalip Indian Reservation, Cultural Resource Assessment, Snohomish County: black and white prints and report., 1986 (Box-folder 8/10, Project 198608.3)
- Pull-and-be-damned Road Improvements, Swinomish Indian Reservation, Cultural Resource Assessment, Skagit County: black and white prints and report., 1986 (Box-folder 8/11, Project 198608.4)
- Proposed Recreational Development at Lake Sammamish State Park, Cultural Resource Investigation, Issaquah, King County: report., 1986 (Box-folder 8/12, Project 198609)
- Cedar River Watershed, Cultural Resources Secondary Use Analysis, for Seattle Water Department, King County: task and alternatives reports., 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/13, Project 198701)
- Harding Creek Mariculture Project, International Marine Farms, Inc., Cultural Resource Assessment, Kitsap County: field notes; maps; report., 1987 (Box-folder 8/14, Project 198702)
- Proposed Hydroelectric Projects along Selected Portions of the Upper Skykomish Drainage, Phase I Cultural Resource Overview for Pacific Hydro, King and Snohomish Counties: report., 1988 (Box-folder 8/15, Project 198703.1)
- Proposed Hydroelectric Projects along Selected Portions of the Upper Skykomish Drainage, Documentation of Indian Religious Use in Project Areas for Pacific Hydro, King and Snohomish Counties: correspondence and report., 1983, 1989 (Box-folder 9/1, Project 198703.2)
- Proposed Hydroelectric Projects on Proctor, Burn, Duffey, Harlan, and Martin Creeks, Tributary to the Skykomish River, Phase II Cultural Resource Reconnaissance for Pacific Hydro, King and Snohomish Counties: reports., 1989 (Box-folder 9/2, Project 198703.3)
- Proposed Hydroelectric Projects along Selected Portions of the Upper Skykomish Drainage, Martin Creek Drainage, Phase I Cultural Resource Overview for Pacific Hydro, King and Snohomish Counties: report., 1990 (Box-folder 9/3, Project 198703.4)
- Cedar River Watershed, Cultural Resources Secondary Use Analysis - American Indian Religious Use - for Seattle Public Utilities (Water Department), King County: report., 1987 (Box-folder 9/4, Project 198706.1)
- Chester Morse Lake Probable Maximum Flood Pool, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance subcontracted under the Center for Northwest Anthropology (Pullman, WA), King County: report., 1988 (Box-folder 9/5, Project 198706.2)